Now, draw your sword!
I challenge you to a fair duel!
Uh... Did I do something?
Please stop feigning innocence.
Fifty-six incidents of violence
with other warriors.
Twenty cases of destroying property.
It's only been a month since
we returned from the Great Ravine...
However did you manage all this?
Yo, I think she's trying to sound like Roxy.
And she sucks at it!
These were all cases
where someone came at me.
Sucks being popular, huh?
Regardless, I can't overlook
any further violent disputes.
What am I supposed to do?
Join the royal army.
Once you do, even the rowdier warriors
will be reluctant to cause trouble for you.
I appreciate the concern,
but I'm not much of a follower.
Gotta have our freedom, after all.
I had anticipated that kind of response.
If you intend to refuse,
then you'll need to reflect
on your actions in a cell.
I'd rather not.
Leaving it in the scabbard?
Don't be upset if it breaks.
It's specially made.
I have no intention of holding back!
Heavy...
Death March
I should have the edge in terms of stats,
but I can't overpower her!
That's a holy knight for you.
I told you, I don't intend on holding back!
This is the kind of technical skill
you get with daily training...
Lost in thought in the midst of battle?!
Aiming for the mask?!
If you won't take this seriously,
I'll expose you... literally.
Hey—
Yeah, yeah, go go, Lady Roxy!
So fast!
Is that Physical Boost?!
You can't win if all you do is dodge.
If you don't want to reveal who you are,
then please, take this seriously.
If that's what you want...
Then I'll have to.
That's...
That power... it's the Holy
Sword Technique skill!
How can you use it without a holy sword?
I told you: This scabbard is specially made.
It's actually a weapon add-on
that improves Holy Sword Techniques
made from the magic crystal
I gathered at the Great Ravine.
If you have the skill
to wield arts in that fashion...
Are you a former holy knight?
Nope.
I'm not the same person, anymore.
I'm just a warrior.
Lady Roxy's gonna lose!
Now I win—
That's... from the gemstone...
Hey! Fate!
You were open.
You total dumbass!
You win.
As if Lady Roxy could ever lose
to that boneheaded bastard!
Why did you suddenly ease up?
I don't know what you mean.
Don't play dumb!
Give me a break. Haven't you done enough?
It's time that I—
Your swordplay...
The way you fight... did you
learn that from Sir Aaron?
I was instructed by him during
my journey here, so I can tell.
The way you strike and your
footwork remind me of his.
Sir Aaron said...
After meeting a traveler
who was headed to Galia,
I decided to take up the sword once more.
And he said that this traveler had a power
that was so great as to cause him difficulty.
If that's you, I'd like to—
Even if it was me, it's my problem.
You need to focus on being able
to protect yourself in Galia.
Lady Roxy... you've always
been so kind, and honest.
Even with a threat to your life
drawing closer...
You're still worried about me.
That was really impressive,
considering you were fighting Lady Roxy.
Mugan.
No wonder you can slay a chimera.
It was being controlled by someone else.
You think so too, then?
It had the same emblem as the salamanders.
Is Eris behind it?
Afterwards, I got a good look
at the chimera...
Pretty wild thinking
to use a monster as the core.
I'm impressed you could figure out
that much just from looking at it.
My family has studied lost Galian
technology for generations.
My late father was, and my
daughter is, a gifted scholar.
Great, a doting dad.
She's nothing like me! Really clever.
The chimera are artificial monsters
made with Galian technology.
It might be a good idea to have
your daughter examine one.
You trying to say you
want me to introduce you?
No, that's not what I meant at all...
You don't get to meet Raine!
Seriously! That's not what
I was trying to say!
What did you mean, then?!
It was just a suggestion!
This guy's less a doting dad
and more a plain old dumbass!
Say, Raine, did you hear about Rafale?
There's something going on
with the Vlerick heir?
Did Hado dying drive him nuts or something?
That might be part of it.
The rumors say he's locked himself in his
room, studying the philosopher's stone.
The philosopher's stone?
He got his hands on it in Tenbern, apparently.
He went on a research trip there
before Hado died.
The philosopher's stone...?
The philosopher's stone... here it is.
It can supposedly heal any wound.
That's amazing!
It can also grant its owner great strength...
Power?
But in exchange, it dominates the mind
and body of the owner.
That's...
Mind-control.
What do you suppose he's planning?
No idea.
The Domain of E.
That's what you should aim for.
What's the Domain of E?
It's the level of power
that the Divine Dragon is at.
If you can't make it there,
you won't be able to fight it.
But if you push too hard, your skill will
overwhelm you, and you'll lose control.
How am I going to get that strong...?
That alarm...
Lady Roxy.
There's a massive stampede...
a death march underway.
We'll move to intercept it.
We march to Galia!
Run for it!
So that's a death march.
The royal army...
You gonna play hero again?
If it's just the death march,
Lady Roxy should be able to deal with it.
Going into a half-starved state, huh?
You've got a better handle on it than before.
We'll want to be ready to move at any time.
We need to figure out
what's going on and end it.
What's going on, huh? Don't think
we'll be waiting long, Fate.
What?
Something's approaching
the royal army from the east.
I don't see anything...
Is it underground?!
It's moving through ground
the way a whale swims.
Seems like a big one.
If it keeps on that path, it'll be
right beneath the royal army soon!
Roxy and the others are
focused on the death march.
They'll be in big trouble if they're
hit with a surprise attack.
Dammit... Greed, you know what to do!
As you wish!
The same way Aaron was able to surpass
his limits thanks to the Gluttony skill...
I can use Gluttony to amplify the charged
shot, and give it twice as much range!
A modified art, only
usable in half-starvation status,
Charged Shot Spiral!
Boosting the range and penetration, huh?
That's a good idea.
I can't always rely on the secret
techniques with how pricey they are.
Here it comes!
See that?! I caught a big one!
That emblem!
It's the same one from before...
This time we're gonna
find out what's behind it!
What's with you? Why the laughing?
I was just thinking... the old me would've
never thought of jumping from so high up.
What're you on about?
Time to tell me who you are!
Violator of the Ground
Omega Slime
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Corrosion,
Stamina Boost (Large)
A Crowned beast...
Its stamina, magic, and spirit
are all over ten million.
Even a holy knight would be
on their back foot against this thing.
Switch me to the magic shield!
What is this?!
Strong acid.
It's raining acid?!
And it smells awful...
Corrosion magic can add corrosive
effects to physical attacks.
So a blend of acid and corrosion magic...
It must've been using this to dissolve
the ground to swim through.
You'll be dead if it touches you.
Watch yourself.
We won't be able to
fight up close at this rate.
And if you slice it up,
and it sprays that acid everywhere,
it'll melt even your bones into a sludge.
Seriously, quit trying to gross me out!
Well, what're you gonna do now?
Take your 10%!
And then we'll add a fire
enchantment to the secret technique!
Let's evaporate him!
Did that do it?
It's gone?
How'd it even pull that?!
It split up and continued the attack. I see.
It protected itself from my secret
technique with one of its offspring.
That direction!
It's headed towards the royal army!
Hold it—
Fate!
They're trying to slow me down...
Grand Cross!
It looked like they were ignoring you,
despite how tasty a snack you'd be...
but it was actually a feint.
Not the kind of move a monster would pull.
It's only got one core.
After moving underground, it's going to
have to surface at this crevice.
When it shows itself, I'll take aim
and smash the core!
Greed! Take 20%!
And then add this, too!
A Charged Shot Spiral Bloody Ptarmigan!
Seriously...?! You really wanna try this
without any practice first?!
It should be able to pass through
any decoys and reach the core.
And I bet you can manage to control it, too.
Well, obviously!
There!
Gluttony skill has activated.
What was that...?
What's going on here? I took its soul, but...
Why is it still alive?
A perception-altering mask, like mine?
Is it Eris? That damned copycat!
Let's see your face, Eris!
That's a Weapon of Mortal Sin!
The Black Gun-Sword, Envy!
That makes it pretty likely
that's Eris holding it.
Oh, I see now.
You saw how the slime was hit
with something before?
It was some kind of magic bullet
that draws out latent power.
That's why it's still alive without a core?
Right.
The core itself became capable
of splitting up, which it did to survive.
An enemy capable of infinite replication...
makes a terrible match for you, I'm afraid.
H-Hey! Here it comes, Fate!
Fate... did you...?
Holding your breath isn't fun.
The Omega Slime's corrosion magic...
you already figured it out?
I'm fighting like a glutton, right?
Gluttony skill has activated.
I was just thinking I hadn't eaten enough.
Don't overdo it.
The slimes won't be a match for me now.
If your stats spike too suddenly,
it can drive your skill into overdrive!
Before that happens...
I'm taking Eris down!
Deflected?!
Take a look at your stats.
You've gone as far as a human can.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony, Identify, Telepathy
Conceal, Night Vision, Brawler,
Holy Sword Technique
One-Handed Sword Technique,
Two-Handed Sword Technique
Strength Boost (Low)
Strength Boost (Med)
Strength Boost (Large)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost  (Med)
Agility Boost (Med)
Health Regen
Stamina Boost (Large)
Corrosion
You'd need to reach inhuman heights...
the Domain of E to go any further.
Then my attacks didn't work...
Because someone who's made it
into the Domain of E
would be immune to anyone else's attacks.
Dammit!
You're wasting your time.
It's not Eris?!
He's... so much stronger...
But I can't afford to wait...
I need to be ready to kill...
and ready to die...
No matter what the price is!
You're finished.
So...
Give me the power I need!
Gluttony skill!
This power... it can't be...
The Domain of E...!
I owe you for this.
If I hadn't run into you,
I wouldn't have made it this far.
Let's go!
Stay out of my way!
I can see his shots clearly now!
A smokescreen?
Northern?!
You're half right.
Half right? What do you mean?
Good question.
But I'm more cautious than Eris is.
A flute? What're you doing?
You'll see soon.
Divine Dragon!
Fate, it's heading westward!
Lady Roxy...!
Probably only needs another 30 seconds.
Dammit!
And now the Divine Dragon and I will
give everything we have to kill her!
So let's see you give everything to stop us!
Fate, in front of you!
A wall of slimes?!
He's obviously trying to buy time.
This bastard...!
Dammit, I need to hurry!
What is that thing?!
The Divine Dragon! All of you, get to safety!
Father...
Lend me your strength!
Lady Roxy!
Not on my watch!
Fay?
Is that you, Fay?
It's been a while...
Lady Roxy.
Devouring
"Devouring."